exports.reservedQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'Acid rain happens because',
    options: ['Sun heats up the upper layer of the atmosphere', 'burning of fossil fuels releases oxides of carbon, nitrogen and sulphur in the atmosphere', 'electrical charges are produced due to friction amongst clouds', 'earth atmosphere contains acids'],
    answer: 'burning of fossil fuels releases oxides of carbon, nitrogen and sulphur in the atmosphere',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    userId: '62d3a759e485f500120e2ffd',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Select the important factor for the site selection of a thermal power plant.',
    options: ['Distance from the populated area', 'Availability of fuel', 'Availability of water', 'Cost of plant'],
    answer: 'Availability of water',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    userId: '62d0f4bde3aba708a86dcb9b',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Acid rain happens because:',
    options: ['sun leads to heating of upper layer of atmosphere.', 'burning of fossil fuels release oxides of carbon', 'nitrogen and sulphur in the atmosphere', 'electrical charges are produced due to friction amongst clouds.', 'earth atmosphere contains acids.'],
    answer: 'burning of fossil fuels release oxides of carbon',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    userId: '62d15557640f7f00128a059b',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  { question: 'Which energy source is the largest source used in India?',
    options: ['CNG', 'LPG', 'Coal', 'Bio Gas'],
    answer: 'LPG',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    userId: '62d1ae07e485f500120e2fee',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  { question: 'The main constituent of CNG is',
    options: ['butane', 'methane', 'ethane', 'propane'],
    answer: 'methane',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    userId: '62d16902640f7f00128a05a1',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  { question: 'The major constituent of biogas is methane.',
    options: ['Both A and R are true and R is the correct explanation of (a)',
      'Both A and R are true but R is not the correct explanation of (a)',
      'A is true but R is false.',
      'A is false but R is true.',
      'Both A and R are false.'],
    answer: 'A is true but R is false.',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    userId: '62d16902640f7f00128a05a1',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following problem is associated with a burning of coal?',
    options: ['Carbon-dioxide emission',
      'acid rain',
      'ash with toxic metal supurity',
      'All of the above'],
    answer: 'All of the above',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    userId: '62d1ae07e485f500120e2fee',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'A solar water heater cannot be used to get hot water on',
    options: ['a sunny day',
      'a cloudy day',
      'a hot day',
      'a windy day'],
    answer: 'a cloudy day',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    userId: '62d16902640f7f00128a05a1',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is the ultimate source of energy for us?',
    options: ['LPG',
      'Nuclear',
      'Solar',
      'CNG'],
    answer: 'Solar',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    userId: '62d1ae07e485f500120e2fee',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which is the ultimate source of energy?',
    options: ['Water',
      'Sun',
      'Uranium',
      'Fossil fuels'],
    answer: 'Sun',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    userId: '62d1ae07e485f500120e2fee',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which method is used to produce electricity in hydroelectric power plant.',
    options: ['By boiling the water to produce steam',
      'By ionizing water',
      'By running dynamo by kinetic energy',
      'Any of the above'],
    answer: 'By running dynamo by kinetic energy',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'easy',
    userId: '62d1ae07e485f500120e2fee',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },
  {
    question: 'Tidal energy is harnessed by constructing a dam across',
    options: ['narrow opening to the sea',
      'wide opening to the sea',
      'the river in hilly trains',
      'the river in plane areas'],
    answer: 'narrow opening to the sea',
    status: 'pending',
    standard: '10',
    topic: ['Sources of energy'],
    subject: 'Science',
    imageKey: null,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    userId: '62d5118c9436470a73d925f5',
    answerExplanation: null,
    feedback: null,
    createdAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
    updatedAt: '2022-08-09 20:19:38.289418+00:00',
  },

];
